<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SN</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string-array name="roi_titles">
        <item>Idea Security</item>
        <item>Initial Chat and Prototyping</item>
        <item>Complete Product Development</item>
        <item>Post Market Support</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="roi_description">
        <item>Your idea is of utmost importance to us. All our discussions begin with an Non Disclosure Agreement (NDA) and securing your ideas as a IP.</item>
        <item>You can discuss your idea with our team without any commitment.We will align our Subject matter expert to answer your queries and come up
         with working prototype in First Sprint cycle.</item>
        <item>Subject matter experts will develop product ,with your team taking shots and product review at every stage of Development.</item>
        <item>We extends post market support to our partners to address customer queries.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="expertise_description">
        <item>Persona, User Journey, Flowchart, Visual Design, Wire-frame, Assets Creation, Prototyping and Template Collections.</item>
        <item>Web App Development, Website Optimization, Social Integration, Boot Strap with Responsive Web Experience to the USERS.</item>
        <item>Technology Partner for full Stack Development across Multiple platforms - Android, iPhone OS, Windows with LAMP, MEAN and Cloud.</item>
        <item>Developing Embedded Software Components, Software Porting, Software Integration, Software Testing on Linux and other Operating System for Connected Devices and SOC.</item>
        <item>Cloud - Specialised in developing software in cloud and PAAS Platform.</item>
        <item>Working as a On-line Branding Partner for clients, with expertise in running successful Digital Campaigns across On-line Social Channels.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
